Local 1199 Drug Division Records 5206-D
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Gettlemen's Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Gilman Pharmacy, 1940-1952 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Gimbels, 1964-1965 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Glove Canteen Inc., 1971 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Goldberg Pharmacy, 1953-1954 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Gold's Drug, 1952 (Box 101, Folder 13)
- Goody Drug, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Gottesman Pharmacy, 1945 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Graham Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- Gralla Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 101, Folder 17)
- Gramercy Pharmacy, 1963 (Box 101, Folder 18)
- Greg Pharmacy, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 19)
- Greenpoint Pharmacy, 1944 (Box 101, Folder 20)
- Gregorius Drug, 1963 (Box 101, Folder 21)
- Greystone Pharmacy, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 22)
- Grove Drug, 1951 (Box 101, Folder 23)
- Grupper Pharmacy, 1940-1966 (Box 101, Folder 24)
- Guth's Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 101, Folder 25)
- Hadley Chemists, 1950 (Box 101, Folder 26)
- Halpern Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 101, Folder 27)
- Hamilton Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Hampton Discount Center, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Hampton Discount Center, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Hampton Discount Center, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Hancock Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Hanover Drug, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Harlem Drug, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Harrico Drug, 1939-1940 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- Harrico-Broadway Drug, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 9)
- Hartley Chemists, 1953-1955 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- Harvey Drug, 1940 (Box 102, Folder 11)
- Harvin Pharmacy, 1955 (Box 102, Folder 12)
- Health Drug Stores, 1957 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Health Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Heights Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Heimlich Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Helena Cut-Rate, 1940 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Higbie Garden Pharmacy, 1963 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Hill Chemists, 1940 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Hillson Drug Co., 1952 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Hitchcock Pharmacy, 1940-1953 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- Hotel McAlpin Pharmacy, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- Hotel St. George, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- Hudson Drug, 1940-1966 (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Hudson National Inc., 1966-1971 (Box 103, Folder 13)
- Inwood Drug Store, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 14)
- J.E. Thomas Pharmacy, 1958 (Box 103, Folder 15)
- Jack's Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 16)
- Jackson Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 17)
- Jacob's Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 18)
- Jamal Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 19)
- Jay-cee Drug, 1950-1952 (Box 103, Folder 20)
- Jaynet Drug, 1945-1946 (Box 103, Folder 21)
- Jewel Drug (Box 103, Folder 22)
- Johnson Juniper Pharmacy, 1962 (Box 103, Folder 23)
- Jurow's Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 103, Folder 24)
- Kahn's Chemists, 1945-1946 (Box 103, Folder 25)
- Kander's Pharmacy, 1951-1952 (Box 103, Folder 26)
- Kardon Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 27)
- Kaufman Pharmacy, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 28)
- Kaufman-Bedrick, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 29)
- Ker-Vin Luncheonette, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 30)
- Kern Drug, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 31)
- Kew Gardens Pharmacy, 1950-1956 (Box 103, Folder 32)
- Kings County Research Labs, 1966-1968 (Box 103, Folder 33)
- Klingman Pharmacy, 1952 (Box 103, Folder 34)
- Ko-Ed Katerers, 1959-1961 (Box 103, Folder 35)
- Kozan Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 103, Folder 36)
- L & S Drug, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 37)
- La Fe Pharmacy, 1951-1952 (Box 103, Folder 38)
- Lawrence Pharmacy, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 39)
- Leach Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 103, Folder 40)
- Lederman Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 41)
- LeFrak City Pharmacy, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 42)
- Lesell Pharmacy, 1952 (Box 103, Folder 43)
- Lexington Chemists, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 44)
- Lichtenstein Pharmacy, 1951-1952 (Box 103, Folder 45)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 12)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- Liggett-Correspondence, 1939-1972 (Box 104, Folder 16)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Allied Trade Council, 1949-1951 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Arbitration, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Areas, 1951-1954 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Areas, 1951-1954 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Areas, 1951-1954 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Areas, 1951-1954 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Forms, 1946 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Leaflets, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 8)
- Liggett-Subject Files: National Labor Relations Board, 1950-1951 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Liggett-Subject Files: National Labor Relations Board, 1950-1951 (Box 105, Folder 10)
- Liggett-Subject Files: National Labor Relations Board, 1950-1951 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Negotiations, 1948-1956 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Negotiations, 1948-1956 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Negotiations, 1948-1956 (Box 105, Folder 14)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Negotiations, 1948-1956 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Negotiations, 1948-1956 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Negotiations, 1948-1956 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Steward Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 105, Folder 18)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Steward Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Strike, 1950-1954 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Strike, 1950-1954 (Box 105, Folder 21)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Strike, 1950-1954 (Box 105, Folder 22)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Strike, 1950-1954 (Box 105, Folder 23)
- Liggett-Subject Files: Wage Survey, 1950-1952 (Box 105, Folder 24)
- Linden Drugs, 1954-1955 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Lipco Drug, 1946 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Lynn Pharmacy, 1954-1955 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Lynette Drug, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Lyon Pharmacy, 1950 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Macy and Co., 1964 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Madison Avenue Chemists, 1951-1952 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Marrud Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Massapeque Park Drug, 1964 (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Master Chemists, 1942 (Box 106, Folder 10)
- Melburt Products Cooperative, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Metro Pharmacy, 1955 (Box 106, Folder 12)
- Metropolitan Diagnostic Labs, 1968-1970 (Box 106, Folder 13)
- Metropolitan Diagnostic Labs, 1968-1970 (Box 106, Folder 14)
- Metropolitan Diagnostic Labs, 1968-1970 (Box 106, Folder 15)
- Miller Terminal Drug Co., 1951-1952 (Box 106, Folder 16)
- Mishkin Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 106, Folder 17)
- Morton Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 106, Folder 18)
- Moss Pharmacy, 1950-1963 (Box 106, Folder 19)
- Mt. Morris Pharmacy, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 20)
- N.S. Drug Co., 1965 (Box 106, Folder 21)
- Nalord Cafeteria, 1956 (Box 106, Folder 22)
- Nassau Drug, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 23)
- Nemiroff, 1957 (Box 106, Folder 24)
- Nescott, Inc., 1965-1971 (Box 106, Folder 25)
- Nescott, Inc., 1965-1971 (Box 106, Folder 26)
- Nescott, Inc., 1965-1971 (Box 106, Folder 27)
- New Yorker Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 106, Folder 28)
- North Village Green Pharmacy, 1953 (Box 106, Folder 29)
- Nottingham Pharmacy, 1957 (Box 106, Folder 30)
- Olympic Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Packard Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Palan Drug, 1946 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Park Slope Pharmacy, 1959 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Park Surgical Co., 1954-1957 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Park Surgical Co., 1954-1957 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Pencal Drug, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania Drug, 1947 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- Penny Profit, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- Perfect Photo, Inc., 1966-1970 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Phelps Drug, 1950-1954 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Platt Drug, 1950-1955 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Plaza Pharmacy, 1952-1953 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- Plazmont Pharmacy, 1947-1952 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- Popelowsky Pharmacy, 1947 (Box 107, Folder 15)
- Princeton Chemists, 1953-1954 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- Project Pryme, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- Pure Labs, 1965-1968 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Pure Labs, 1965-1968 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Pure Labs, 1965-1968 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- RXD Prescription Centers, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Ralph Drug, 1951-1952 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Red Arrow Pharmacy, 1951-1952 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Reed Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Regency Pharmacy, 1959 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Regnal Drug, 1955 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Rego Pharmacy, 1952 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Reliable Drug, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Reuben Bel fas Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Rex Associates, 1953 (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Rite Aid Pharmacy, 1968-1971 (Box 108, Folder 14)
- Rival Drug, 1954-1955 (Box 108, Folder 15)
- Romanoff Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 108, Folder 16)
- Rosenberg Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Royal Drug, 1954-1969 (Box 108, Folder 18)
- S & K Drug, 1955 (Box 108, Folder 19)
- S & 0 Drug, 1946 (Box 108, Folder 20)
- St. George Pharmacy, 1954 (Box 108, Folder 21)
- Salem Drug, 1963 (Box 108, Folder 22)
- Salud Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- Sam's Orchard St. Drug Corp., 1964 (Box 108, Folder 24)
- Sam's Wholesale, 1964 (Box 108, Folder 25)
- Schultz Pharmacy, 1953 (Box 108, Folder 26)
- Select Drug, 1950-1952 (Box 108, Folder 27)
- Seventh Avenue Ethical Pharmacy, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 28)
- Seymour Drug Corp., 1951-1952 (Box 108, Folder 29)
- Shally Pharmacy, 1957 (Box 108, Folder 30)
- Shear's Pharmacy, 1960 (Box 108, Folder 31)
- 666 Drug Co., 1959 (Box 108, Folder 32)
- Spector Bros., 1946 (Box 108, Folder 33)
- Spencer Chemists, 1940 (Box 108, Folder 34)
- Star Drug, 1953 (Box 108, Folder 35)
- Stevlin's 98, 1963 (Box 108, Folder 36)
- Strathmore Drugs, 1956 (Box 108, Folder 37)
- Student Drug, 1946 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Super B Drug Store, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Super X, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Supermarkets, 1965-1971 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Supermarkets, 1965-1971 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Supermarkets, 1965-1971 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Tee & Tee Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Temple Pharmacy, 1940 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Theresa Pharmacy, 1946 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Thrift-way Drug, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Tilson Pharmacy, 1952 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Times Square Stores, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Tino's Luncheonette, 1970-1971 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Towne Pharmacy, 1961 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Trio Drug, 1946 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Union News Drug, 1951 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- Union Square Pharmacy, 1955 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- Unity Drug, 1953-1954 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- University Chemists, 1955 (Box 109, Folder 19)
- Victoria Pharmacy, 1959 (Box 109, Folder 20)
- Waldorf Astoria Pharmacy, 1960 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Walgreen Company, 1950-1952 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Webster Drugs, 1940-1952 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- Westbridge Pharmacy, 1956 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Whelan-Correspondence, 1955-1970 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Arbitration Cases, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Area (Bronx-West Midtown), 1951-1954 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Area (Bronx-West Midtown), 1951-1954 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Area (Bronx-West Midtown), 1951-1954 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Area (Bronx-West Midtown), 1951-1954 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Area (Bronx-West Midtown), 1951-1954 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Area (Bronx-West Midtown), 1951-1954 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Forms, 1945 (Box 113, Folder 8)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Grievances, 1964-1971 (Box 113, Folder 9)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Grievances, 1964-1971 (Box 113, Folder 10)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Health Insurance, 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 11)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Leaflets, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 12)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Meetings, Category, 1956 (Box 113, Folder 13)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Membership, 1950-1966 (Box 113, Folder 14)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Membership, 1950-1966 (Box 113, Folder 15)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Membership, 1950-1966 (Box 113, Folder 16)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: National Labor Relations Board, 1950-1951 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: National Labor Relations Board, 1950-1951 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Negotiations, 1950-1966 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Negotiations, 1950-1966 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Negotiations, 1950-1966 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Negotiations, 1950-1966 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Negotiations, 1950-1966 (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Negotiations, 1950-1966 (Box 114, Folder 8)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Negotiations, 1950-1966 (Box 114, Folder 9)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Philadelphia Organization, 1952-1953 (Box 114, Folder 10)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Shoppers Reports, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Strikes, 1937-1952 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Strikes, 1937-1952 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Strikes, 1937-1952 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Strikes, 1937-1952 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Strikes, 1937-1952 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Strikes, 1937-1952 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Strikes, 1937-1952 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Strikes, 1937-1952 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- Whelan Drug-Subject files: Survey, 1950-1952 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- World Merchandise Exchange, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- A (Box 116)
- B (Box 117)
- B (Box 118)
- C (Box 119)
- C (Box 120)
- D (Box 121)
- E-F (Box 122)
- E-F (Box 123)
- G (Box 124)
- H (Box 125)
- H (Box 126)
- J-K (Box 127)
- K-L (Box 128)
- L (Box 129)
- M-N (Box 130)
- M-N (Box 131)
- O-P (Box 132)
- P (Box 133)
- R (Box 134)
- S (Box 135)
- S (Box 136)
- T-U (Box 137)
- V-W (Box 138)
- W-Z (Box 139)
- Broadside, 1929 (Box 140, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Problems, 1938-1964 (Box 140, Folder 2)
- Strike News Clippings, 1941 (Box 140, Folder 3)
- March of Dimes Certificate of Appreciation, 1950 (Box 140, Folder 4)
- "Teen Time at 1199", 1955-1957 (Box 140, Folder 5)
- Feature Articles on 1199, 1955-1961 (Box 140, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Education News and Views, 1957 (Box 140, Folder 7)
- Know Your Union, 1961 (Box 140, Folder 8)
- Fast for Peace [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  March 24, 1968
- Fast for Peace [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 140, Folder 10)
- Drug Division Delegates Newsletter, 1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 11)
- What's On At Local 1199, 1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 12)
- 1199 Duplicate Photographs (Box 140, Folder 13)
- Coretta Scott King Message to Hospital and Nursing Home Members (Box 140, Folder 14)
  Pasteboard 33 1/3 rpm record with text on the back side.
- Song Lyrics (Box 140, Folder 15)
  Two printed lyric sheets
- "Union Store" Signs (Box 140, Folder 16)
  Two metal signs to display in store windows.
- 1199 Drug News, 1947-1950 (Box 142)
  January-October, December 1947 February-December 1948 January-December 1949 (Complete) January-December 1950 (Complete)
- 1130 News, 1944 (Box 141)
  January, March, April 1944
- 1130 News, 1943 (Box 141)
  July-August, December 1943
- 1199 News, 1942 (Box 141)
  January-March, May, June 1942 July-September 1942
- Retail Drug Worker, 1940-1941 (Box 141)
  August-December 1940 January-March, May, July-November 1941
- Local 1199 Drug Worker, 1940 (Box 141)
  Special edition
- Retail Drug Worker, 1939-1939 (Box 141)
  August, October, November, December 1938 January, March, April, May, July, August 1939
- Union Pharmacist, 1934-1935 (Box 141)
  March 1934 February 1935 July 1934 June 1935
- Voice of the Mortar & Pestle, 1929 (Box 141)
  v.1 (1929:Mar.)
- 1199 Drug News, 1944-1946 (Box 141)
  July 1944 September, November, December 1944 February-December 1945 January-December 1946 (Complete)
- 1199 Drug News, 1951-1961 (Box 143)
  January-March, May-August, October-December 1951 January-December 1952 (Complete) January-December 1953 (Complete) January-April, June-December 1954 January-June, September-December 1955 March, June 1956 March 1961
- 1199 Drug & Hospital News, 1968-1972 (Box 144)
  February-July, September-December 1968 January-June, September-December 1969 January-December 1970 (Complete) January-December 1971 (Complete) January-June, August-December 1972
- Text digitized from the collection. (Box 144)